Guide to the Argus Book Shop Correspondence
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1857, 1920-1955; Series I; 5.0 linear feet (13 boxes)
  - Lapham, Edward A., 1942 (Box 7, Folder 251)
  - Laves, Gerhardt, 1941 Nov 10 (Box 7, Folder 252)
  - Lee, Alfred P. (Alfred Pyle), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 253)
  - Lee, Irving J., 1943 Feb 9 (Box 7, Folder 254)
  - Lee, Manfred B. (Manfred Bennington), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 255)
  - Leighton, Clare, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 256)
  - Leonard, William Ellery, 1929-1941 (Box 7, Folder 257)
  - Lesser, Simon O., 1942 (Box 7, Folder 258)
  - Levant, Oscar, 1940 Nov 6 (Box 7, Folder 259)
  - Levin, Meyer, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 260)
  - Lewis, Herbert Clyde, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 261)
  - Lewis, Sinclair, 1932-1940 (Box 7, Folder 262)
  - Lawrence, Frieda von Richthofen, 1933, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 263)
  - Leacock, Stephen, 1943 Mar 19 (Box 7, Folder 264)
  - Leginska, Ethel, 1936 Nov 27 (Box 7, Folder 265)
  - Lewisohn, Ludwig and Edna, 1932-1943 (Box 7, Folder 266)
  - Lindsay, Norman and Rose, 1936-1944 (Box 7, Folder 267)
  - Lipton, Lawrence, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 268)
  - Little, Shelby, 1929 Jul 2 (Box 7, Folder 269)
  - Lofting, Hugh, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 270)
  - London, Jack, undated (Box 7, Folder 271)
    Contains only an undated photostat of a 1914 letter from London to Ralph Kasper
  - London, Joan, 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 272)
  - Lowry, Katherine, 1932 Jul 6 (Box 7, Folder 273)
  - Lowry, Robert
  - Lundquist, Matthew Nathanael, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 274)
  - Lyons, Eugene, 1937, undated (Box 7, Folder 275)
  - McAlmon, Robert, 1929-1930 (Box 7, Folder 276)
  - McCullers, Carson, 1940-1942 (Box 7, Folder 277)
  - McCutcheon, John T. (John Tinney) and Evelyn, 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 278)
  - MacDonald, Jessica North, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 279)
  - McEvoy, J. P. (Joseph Patrick), 1941 Dec 26 (Box 7, Folder 280)
  - McFee, William, 1930-1942 (Box 7, Folder 281)
  - MacIntyre, Carlyle Ferren, 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 282)
  - McIver, Claude Searcy, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 283)
  - McKay, Allis, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 284)
  - MacLeish, Archibald, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 285)
  - McWilliams, Carey, 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 286)
  - Mann, George, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 287)
  - Mann, Thomas, 1940 Aug 1 (Box 8, Folder 288)
  - Marks, Stanley J., 1943-1944 (Box 8, Folder 289)
  - Martin, George Victor, 1941-1944 (Box 8, Folder 290)
  - Martin, John Bartlow and Frances R., 1942-1944 (Box 8, Folder 291)
  - Mason, F. van Wyck (Francis van Wyck), 1940 (Box 8, Folder 292)
  - Mason, Walt, undated (Box 8, Folder 293)
  - Masters, Edgar Lee and Marcia, 1935-1943 (Box 8, Folder 294)
  - Mathers, E. Powys (Edward Powys), 1933 Oct 23 (Box 8, Folder 295)
  - Maugham, W. Somerset (William Somerset), 1937-1942 (Box 8, Folder 296)
  - Meagher, Maude, 1936-1941 (Box 8, Folder 297)
  - Meeker, Arthur, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 298)
  - Meloney, William Brown, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 299)
  - Mencken, H. L. (Henry Louis), 1927-1955 (Box 8, Folder 300)
  - Merritt, Jesse, undated (Box 8, Folder 301)
  - Milburn, George, 1939-1942 (Box 8, Folder 302)
  - Millay, Edna St. Vincent, 1933, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 303)
  - Miller, Henry
    - Correspondence, 1937-1955, undated (Box 9, Folder 304-314)
      See also: Houghton, Claude (1944)
      Includes photograph of Anais Nin (1941)
    - Connecticut Anthroposophical Society letters and membership lists, 1938-1940 (Box 9, Folder 315)
      Holds letters requesting copies of Miller's book The Tropic of Cancer
  - Mills, Clark, 1942 Jan 14 (Box 10, Folder 316)
  - Millspaugh, C. A. (Clarence Arthur), 1939 (Box 10, Folder 317)
  - Moore, Doris Langley, 1933 Feb 17 (Box 10, Folder 318)
  - Moore, E. E., 1932 Jul 19 (Box 10, Folder 319)
  - Moore, Harry Thornton, 1942 Jan 28 (Box 10, Folder 320)
  - Moore, Ward, 1941-1942 (Box 10, Folder 321)
  - Morley, Christopher, 1932-1943 (Box 10, Folder 322)
  - Morris, Constance Lily, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 323)
  - Morrison, Nancy Brysson, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 324)
  - Morse, Samuel French, 1941-1944 (Box 10, Folder 325)
  - Mottram, R. H. (Ralph Hale), 1933 Sep 18 (Box 10, Folder 326)
  - Mullally, Donn, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 327)
  - Mulqueen, Elizabeth Costa, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 328)
  - Munson, Knox, 1944 Jun 5 (Box 10, Folder 329)
  - Murdoch, Angus, 1943 Jan 31 (Box 10, Folder 330)
  - Neilson, Francis, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 331)
  - Nielson, Helen Swift
    See: Swift, Helen
  - Nejelski, Leo, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 332)
  - Newhouse, Edward, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 333)
  - Nin, Anais, 1942-1944 (Box 10, Folder 334)
    See also: Miller, Henry (1941)
  - Nonweiler, Arville, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 335)
  - North, Sterling, 1943 Dec 14 (Box 10, Folder 336)
  - Nott, Stanley Charles, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 337)
  - Odets, Clifford, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 338)
  - Olmsted, Nelson, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 339)
  - Osborne, Donna Byrne, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 340)
    Includes photographs of Bunsho Jugaku
  - Papé, Frank Cheyne, 1928-1934 (Box 10, Folder 341-342)
  - Parry, Albert, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 343)
  - Patchen, Kenneth, 1941-1946 (Box 10, Folder 344)
  - Paul, Elliot, 1942 May 4 (Box 10, Folder 345)
  - Paul, Louis, 1936-1943 (Box 10, Folder 346-347)
  - Payne, Gabriel, 1932 Jul 22 (Box 10, Folder 348)
  - Pearson, Hesketh, 1934 Oct 14 (Box 10, Folder 349)
  - Pearson, Norman Holmes, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 350)
  - Peattie, Donald Culross, 1936-1945 (Box 10, Folder 351)
  - Peattie, Roderick, 1941-1942 (Box 11, Folder 352)
  - Peck, Elisabeth Sinclair, 1937 Sep 20 (Box 11, Folder 353)
  - Pegler, J. Westbrook (James Westbrook), 1937 Jul 19 (Box 11, Folder 354)
  - Pennell, Joseph Stanley, 1944-1948 (Box 11, Folder 355)
  - Phelps, William Lyon, 1942 Jul 27 (Box 11, Folder 356)
  - Phillpotts, Eden, 1933 Sep 1 (Box 11, Folder 357)
  - Pierce, Bessie Louise, 1940 Oct 2 (Box 11, Folder 358)
  - Pilgrim, David, 1937 Sep 27 (Box 11, Folder 359)
  - Pinero, Arthur Wing, Sir, 1934 Sep 21 (Box 11, Folder 360)
  - Pound, Ezra, 1933 Dec 24 (Box 11, Folder 361)
  - Prochnow, Herbert V. (Herbert Victor), 1942 (Box 11, Folder 362)
  - Prokosch, Frederic, 1934-1943 (Box 11, Folder 363)
  - Rascoe, Burton, 1932-1941 (Box 11, Folder 364)
  - Rawlings, Marjorie Kinnan, 1941-1944 (Box 11, Folder 365)
  - Rex Brasher Associates, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 366)
  - Rice, Craig, 1940-1943 (Box 11, Folder 367)
  - Ripperger, Helmut, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 368)
  - Robinson, Oliver W., 1943 Aug 7 (Box 11, Folder 369)
  - Rogers, Virginia Horton, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 370)
  - Ruby, Harry, 1943 Aug 10 (Box 11, Folder 371)
  - Rudy, John Forney, 1942 Aug 12 (Box 11, Folder 372)
  - Running, Lillian, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 373)
  - Sandburg, Carl, 1941-1944 (Box 11, Folder 374)
  - Sandoz, Mari, 1941-1944 (Box 11, Folder 375)
  - Sarett, Lew, 1941-1943 (Box 11, Folder 376)
  - Saroyan, William, 1934-1941 (Box 11, Folder 377)
  - Schacher, Gerhard, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 378)
  - Schaller, Robert Clark, 1942-1943 (Box 11, Folder 379)
  - Schorer, Mark, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 380)
  - Schwartz, Delmore, 1942 Nov 28 (Box 11, Folder 381)
  - Sheppard, Harriet, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 382)
  - Shores, Nancy, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 383)
  - Shridharani, Krishnalal, 1941-1942 (Box 11, Folder 384)
  - Siberell, Lloyd Emerson, undated (Box 11, Folder 385)
    Contains checklist of the publications of the Old Capitol Press of David K. Webb
  - Sigerist, Henry E. (Henry Ernest), 1946-1947 (Box 11, Folder 386)
  - Sinclair, Harold, 1932-1941 (Box 11, Folder 387)
  - Smith, Edgar Wadsworth, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 388)
  - Smith, Robert Paul, 1941-1942 (Box 11, Folder 389)
  - Smith, Solomon A., Mrs., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 390)
  - Snower, H. B., 1937 Nov 23 (Box 11, Folder 391)
  - Smyth, Joseph Hilton, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 392)
  - Sorenson, Virginia, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 393)
  - Spectorsky, August, 1943 Nov 26 (Box 11, Folder 394)
  - Starrett, Vincent, 1941-1948 (Box 11, Folder 395)
  - Steele, Dan, 1941-1942 (Box 11, Folder 396)
  - Steinbeck, John and Carol, 1935-1941, undated (Box 12, Folder 397-398)
    Includes informal photographs
    See also: Paul, Louis (1938)
  - Sterling, Alexander Mahan, 1932 Jul 25 (Box 12, Folder 399)
  - Stone, Irving, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 400)
  - Storm, Otto, 1941 Apr 10 (Box 12, Folder 401)
  - Stout, Rex, 1943 May 24 (Box 12, Folder 402)
  - Streit, Clarence K. (Clarence Kirshman), 1944 (Box 12, Folder 403)
  - Struther, Jan, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 404)
  - Suckow, Ruth, 1942 Apr 8 (Box 12, Folder 405)
  - Swabacker, Leslie, 1941-1942 (Box 12, Folder 406)
  - Swift, Helen, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 407)
  - Symons, A. J. A. (Alphonse James Albert), 1937 Feb 18 (Box 12, Folder 408)
  - Terrell, John Upton, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 409)
  - Thayer, Tiffany, 1941-1944 (Box 12, Folder 410)
  - Thomajan, Puzant Kevork, 1942-1943 (Box 12, Folder 411)
  - Thomas, Winfield W., 1949 (Box 12, Folder 412)
  - Thomason, John W. (John William), 1941 (Box 12, Folder 413)
  - Thompson, Sue, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 414)
  - Thorek, Max, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 415)
  - Thornton, Willis, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 416)
  - Tice, Clara, 1936-1941, undated (Box 12, Folder 417)
  - Tooker, Richard, 1943-1944 (Box 12, Folder 418)
  - Toor, Frances, 1943-1944 (Box 12, Folder 419)
  - Townshend, Frank, 1942 Aug 7 (Box 12, Folder 420)
  - Truesdale, Bill, 1944 Jan 1 (Box 12, Folder 421)
  - Ulreich, Nura Woodson, 1935 Jan 19 (Box 12, Folder 422)
  - Untermeyer, Louis, 1940-1948 (Box 12, Folder 423)
  - Vaka, Demetra, 1943 May 12 (Box 12, Folder 424)
  - Von Hagen, Victor Wolfgang, 1939 Dec 17 (Box 12, Folder 425)
  - Wagner, Constance, 1940 Feb 7 (Box 12, Folder 426)
  - Walpole, Hugh, Sir, 1932, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 427)
  - Walton, Evangeline, 1936-1944 (Box 12, Folder 428)
  - Watkin, Lawrence Edward, 1938-1940 (Box 12, Folder 429)
  - Waugh, Alec, 1941 Oct 3 (Box 12, Folder 430)
  - Weber, Carl Jefferson, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 431)
  - Welch, Patrick, 1940-1942 (Box 12, Folder 432)
  - Welch, Roy K., 1940 Jun 25 (Box 12, Folder 433)
  - Wellman, Paul Iselin, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 434)
  - West, Herbert Faulkner, 1936-1939 (Box 12, Folder 435)
  - West, Nathanael, 1937-1940 (Box 12, Folder 436)
  - Wetjen, Albert Richard, 1947 Apr 21 (Box 12, Folder 437)
  - White, E. B. (Elwyn Brooks), 1935 Dec 3 (Box 12, Folder 438)
  - White, Emil, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 439)
  - White, Robb, 1942 Aug 6 (Box 12, Folder 440)
  - White, William Lindsay, 1938 Apr 15 (Box 12, Folder 441)
  - Wiggam, Lionel, 1936-1942 (Box 12, Folder 442)
  - Wigmore, John Henry, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 443)
  - Wilder, Thornton, 1935-1941 (Box 12, Folder 444)
  - Wilkins, Vaughan, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 445)
  - Wilkinson, Louis Umfreville, 1928 Feb 13 (Box 12, Folder 446)
  - Williams, Cecil B. (Cecil Brown), 1944 (Box 13, Folder 447)
  - Williams, Dorcas, 1937 Feb 5 (Box 13, Folder 448)
  - Williams, Oscar, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 449)
  - Willis, Saul B., 1932 Jul 24 (Box 13, Folder 450)
  - Wilson, Edmund, 1946-1951 (Box 13, Folder 451)
  - Winchell, Walter, 1933 Mar 8 (Box 13, Folder 452)
  - Winspear, Elizabeth B., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 453)
  - Winterich, John Tracy, 1934 Dec 27 (Box 13, Folder 454)
  - Winters, Elizabeth R., 1943 (Box 13, Folder 455)
  - Winwar, Frances, 1940-1944 (Box 13, Folder 456)
  - Wise, Thomas James, 1928 Jun 24 (Box 13, Folder 457)
  - Wolff, Maritta, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 458)
  - Wood, Charles Erskine Scott, 1936 (Box 13, Folder 459)
  - Wood, Clement, 1941-1943 (Box 13, Folder 460)
  - Woodford, Jack, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 461)
  - Woollcott, Alexander, 1942 Dec 1 (Box 13, Folder 462)
  - Wright, Richard, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 463)
  - Wyatt, Edith, 1939-1944 (Box 13, Folder 464)
  - Young, June F., 1943 Aug 20 (Box 13, Folder 465)
  - Ziff, William B. (William Bernard), 1943 Aug 4 (Box 13, Folder 466)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1941-1943, undated (Box 13, Folder 467)
    Includes a printed circular letter from Abramson to his shop patrons (undated); a typed carbon copy of a letter from Van Wyck Brooks to "Max" (1941); press release for book on shells by Maxwell Smith (1941); letter from Abramson to "Percy" [Loring?] (1943); collation of edition of Thackeray's Vanity Fair (undated)
- Manuscripts, 1937, undated; Series II; 0.42; (1 box)
  Series II is arranged alphabetically by author.
  The series is comprised of a group of literary essays, poems, and book reviews, predominantly original typescripts, that were likely submitted for Abramson's proposed "Argus miscellany." Some of the manuscripts include photographs meant to be used as text illustrations.
  - Bauer, Thorpe: "Streamlined Scripture", undated (Box 14, Folder 468)
  - Bean, Folsom S.: "Written on a Fly", undated (Box 14, Folder 469)
  - Berg, H. M., Jr.: on O. W. Holmes, Washington Irving, Mary Mapes Dodge, and Henry David Thoreau, undated (Box 14, Folder 470)
  - Braude, Jacob Morton: "I Like Bad Boys", undated (Box 14, Folder 471)
  - Chapin, Helen Burwell: "Reading and Collecting in China", undated (Box 14, Folder 472)
  - Clarke, Norman E. (Norman Ellsworth): "Huckleberry Finn", undated (Box 14, Folder 473)
  - Conklin, Groff: on Ulysses, Bryant, and James Clarence Mangan, undated (Box 14, Folder 474)
  - Dart, Ruth: "We Women Collectors", undated (Box 14, Folder 475)
  - Ege, Otto F.: "The Book Beautiful", undated (Box 14, Folder 476)
  - Guthrie, James: "Edgar Allan Poe: Poet of Landscape", undated (Box 14, Folder 477)
  - Heron, Flodden W.: "An Accidental Portrait of R. L. S.", undated (Box 14, Folder 478)
  - Hockin, John Russell Ayescoghe: "John Brown's Bogey", undated (Box 14, Folder 479)
  - Jones, Dan Burne: "Ex Libris: Bookplate Prints", undated (Box 14, Folder 480)
  - Jones, Louise Seymour: "Chaucer's Gardens," "Taliesin," and untitled poem, undated (Box 14, Folder 481)
  - Kent, William: "Shakespearean Heresy", undated (Box 14, Folder 482)
  - Klinefelter, Walter: "If Ever Falstaff Went to Arthur's Bosom", undated (Box 14, Folder 483)
  - Kuder, Blanche Bane, undated (Box 14, Folder 484)
  - Laughlin, James: "The Publishing Business", undated (Box 14, Folder 485)
  - Levine, Isaac: "The Versatile Mr. Laurence Housman", 1937, undated (Box 14, Folder 486)
    Contains a letter from Laurence Housman to Levine (1937), and a bibliography
  - Mencken, H. L. (Henry Louis): "On Collecting Henrik Ibsen", undated (Box 14, Folder 487)
  - Moore, Edward Martin: "Authors as Typographers" and "Fashions in Type", undated (Box 14, Folder 488)
  - Perry, Louise S. G. (Louise Sanborn Gifford): "Rich Richard the Bookish Bishop", undated (Box 14, Folder 489)
  - Plumb, Charles S. (Charles Sumner): "Notes by a Collector of Bibles", undated (Box 14, Folder 490)
  - Powell, Lawrence Clark: "The Seven Best Books of D. H. Lawrence," and review of Robinson Jeffers poems, undated (Box 14, Folder 491)
  - Prouty, Louise: "The Cleveland Public Library", undated (Box 14, Folder 492)
  - Schultz, William Eben: "A Study in Titles", undated (Box 14, Folder 493)
  - Stone, P. M. (Percival Mason): "Collective Detective Fiction", undated (Box 14, Folder 494)
  - Vaka, Demetra: on first editions, undated (Box 14, Folder 495)
  - VanderPoel, Halsted B.: "And Out of Olde Books", undated (Box 14, Folder 496)
  - Vehling, Joseph Dommers: "Apicus: Cookery and Dining in Ancient Rome", undated (Box 14, Folder 497)
  - Wolf, Geraldine: "Outline of History", undated (Box 14, Folder 498)
  - Wolf, Howard: four essays, undated (Box 14, Folder 499)
  - Unidentified authors, undated (Box 14, Folder 500)
- Restricted Fragile
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folder 1 (Box 15, Folder 501)
  - Box 1, folder 2 (Box 15, Folder 502)
  - Box 1, folder 4 (Box 15, Folder 503)
  - Box 1, folder 5 (Box 15, Folder 504)
  - Box 1, folder 7 (Box 15, Folder 505)
  - Box 1, folder 9 (Box 15, Folder 506)
  - Box 1, folder 11 (Box 15, Folder 507)
  - Box 1, folder 13 (Box 15, Folder 508)
  - Box 1, folder 16 (Box 15, Folder 509)
  - Box 1, folder 20 (Box 15, Folder 510)
  - Box 1, folders 22-29 (Box 15, Folder 511-512)
  - Box 1, folder 30 (Box 15, Folder 513)
  - Box 1, folder 31 (Box 15, Folder 514)
  - Box 1, folder 32 (Box 15, Folder 515)
  - Box 1, folder 36 (Box 15, Folder 516)
  - Box 2, folder 39 (Box 15, Folder 517)
  - Box 2, folder 40 (Box 15, Folder 518)
  - Box 2, folder 42 (Box 15, Folder 519)
  - Box 2, folder 43 (Box 15, Folder 520)
  - Box 2, folder 44 (Box 15, Folder 521)
  - Box 2, folder 52 (Box 15, Folder 522)
  - Box 2, folder 53 (Box 15, Folder 523)
  - Box 2, folder 55 (Box 15, Folder 524)
  - Box 2, folder 57 (Box 15, Folder 525)
  - Box 2, folder 58 (Box 15, Folder 526)
  - Box 2, folder 63 (Box 15, Folder 527)
  - Box 2, folder 64 (Box 15, Folder 528)
  - Box 2, folder 65 (Box 15, Folder 529)
  - Box 2, folder 66 (Box 15, Folder 530)
  - Box 2, folder 67 (Box 15, Folder 531)
  - Box 2, folder 68 (Box 15, Folder 532)
  - Box 2, folder 73 (Box 15, Folder 533)
  - Box 2, folder 75 (Box 15, Folder 534)
  - Box 2, folder 77 (Box 15, Folder 535)
  - Box 2, folder 81 (Box 15, Folder 536)
  - Box 3, folder 85 (Box 15, Folder 537)
  - Box 3, folder 86 (Box 15, Folder 538)
  - Box 3, folder 87 (Box 15, Folder 539)
  - Box 3, folder 89 (Box 15, Folder 540)
  - Box 3, folder 91 (Box 15, Folder 541)
  - Box 3, folder 95 (Box 15, Folder 542)
  - Box 3, folder 96 (Box 15, Folder 543)
  - Box 3, folder 98 (Box 15, Folder 544)
  - Box 3, folder 100 (Box 15, Folder 545)
  - Box 3, folders 101-103 (Box 15, Folder 546-547)
  - Box 3, folder 104 (Box 15, Folder 548)
  - Box 3, folder 106 (Box 15, Folder 549)
  - Box 3, folder 107 (Box 15, Folder 550)
  - Box 3, folder 109 (Box 15, Folder 551)
  - Box 3, folder 110 (Box 15, Folder 552)
  - Box 4, folders 111-119 (Box 15, Folder 553-554)
  - Box 4, folders 111-119 (Box 16, Folder 555-556)
  - Box 4, folder 122 (Box 16, Folder 557)
  - Box 4, folder 124 (Box 16, Folder 558)
  - Box 4, folder 127 (Box 16, Folder 559)
  - Box 5, folders 130-131 (Box 16, Folder 560)
  - Box 5, folder 132 (Box 16, Folder 561)
  - Box 5, folder 134 (Box 16, Folder 562)
  - Box 5, folder 137 (Box 16, Folder 563)
  - Box 5, folder 138 (Box 16, Folder 564)
  - Box 5, folder 139 (Box 16, Folder 565)
  - Box 5, folder 141 (Box 16, Folder 566)
  - Box 5, folder 142 (Box 16, Folder 567)
  - Box 5, folders 144-145 (Box 16, Folder 568)
  - Box 5, folder 146 (Box 16, Folder 569)
  - Box 5, folder 147 (Box 16, Folder 570)
  - Box 5, folder 148 (Box 16, Folder 571)
  - Box 5, folder 150 (Box 16, Folder 572)
  - Box 5, folder 151 (Box 16, Folder 573)
  - Box 5, folder 153 (Box 16, Folder 574)
  - Box 5, folder 156 (Box 16, Folder 575)
  - Box 5, folder 161 (Box 16, Folder 576)
  - Box 5, folder 163 (Box 16, Folder 577)
  - Box 5, folder 164 (Box 16, Folder 578)
  - Box 5, folder 166 (Box 16, Folder 579)
  - Box 5, folder 167 (Box 16, Folder 580)
  - Box 6, folders 170-171 (Box 16, Folder 581)
  - Box 6, folder 173 (Box 16, Folder 582)
  - Box 6, folder 175 (Box 16, Folder 583)
  - Box 6, folder 178 (Box 16, Folder 584)
  - Box 6, folder 180 (Box 16, Folder 585)
  - Box 6, folder 182 (Box 16, Folder 586)
  - Box 6, folder 183 (Box 16, Folder 587)
  - Box 6, folder 185 (Box 16, Folder 588)
  - Box 6, folder 186 (Box 16, Folder 589)
  - Box 6, folder 190 (Box 16, Folder 590)
  - Box 6, folder 191 (Box 16, Folder 591)
  - Box 6, folder 192 (Box 16, Folder 592)
  - Box 6, folders 199-200 (Box 16, Folder 593)
  - Box 6, folder 205 (Box 16, Folder 594)
  - Box 6, folder 206 (Box 16, Folder 595)
  - Box 6, folder 207 (Box 16, Folder 596)
  - Box 6, folder 208 (Box 16, Folder 597)
  - Box 6, folder 210 (Box 16, Folder 598)
  - Box 6, folder 211 (Box 16, Folder 599)
  - Box 6, folder 213 (Box 16, Folder 600)
  - Box 6, folder 216 (Box 16, Folder 601)
  - Box 6, folder 219 (Box 16, Folder 602)
  - Box 7, folder 220 (Box 16, Folder 603)
  - Box 7, folder 222 (Box 16, Folder 604)
  - Box 7, folder 223 (Box 16, Folder 605)
  - Box 7, folder 226 (Box 16, Folder 606)
  - Box 7, folder 227 (Box 16, Folder 607)
  - Box 7, folder 229 (Box 16, Folder 608)
  - Box 7, folder 230 (Box 16, Folder 609)
  - Box 7, folder 233 (Box 16, Folder 610)
  - Box 7, folder 235 (Box 16, Folder 611)
  - Box 7, folder 237 (Box 16, Folder 612)
  - Box 7, folder 239 (Box 16, Folder 613)
  - Box 7, folder 240 (Box 16, Folder 614)
  - Box 7, folder 242 (Box 16, Folder 615)
  - Box 7, folder 244 (Box 16, Folder 616)
  - Box 7, folder 246 (Box 16, Folder 617)
  - Box 7, folder 248 (Box 16, Folder 618)
  - Box 7, folder 249 (Box 16, Folder 619)
  - Box 7, folder 250 (Box 17, Folder 620)
  - Box 7, folder 253 (Box 17, Folder 621)
  - Box 7, folder 255 (Box 17, Folder 622)
  - Box 7, folder 257 (Box 17, Folder 623)
  - Box 7, folder 259 (Box 17, Folder 624)
  - Box 7, folder 260 (Box 17, Folder 625)
  - Box 7, folder 261 (Box 17, Folder 626)
  - Box 7, folder 262 (Box 17, Folder 627)
  - Box 7, folder 266 (Box 17, Folder 628)
  - Box 7, folder 267 (Box 17, Folder 629)
  - Box 7, folder 271 (Box 17, Folder 630)
  - Box 7, folder 274 (Box 17, Folder 631)
  - Box 7, folder 277 (Box 17, Folder 632)
  - Box 7, folder 278 (Box 17, Folder 633)
  - Box 7, folder 279 (Box 17, Folder 634)
  - Box 7, folder 281 (Box 17, Folder 635)
  - Box 8, folder 284 (Box 17, Folder 636)
  - Box 8, folder 285 (Box 17, Folder 637)
  - Box 8, folder 286 (Box 17, Folder 638)
  - Box 8, folder 287 (Box 17, Folder 639)
  - Box 8, folder 288 (Box 17, Folder 640)
  - Box 8, folder 289 (Box 17, Folder 641)
  - Box 8, folder 290 (Box 17, Folder 642)
  - Box 8, folder 291 (Box 17, Folder 643)
  - Box 8, folder 292 (Box 17, Folder 644)
  - Box 8, folder 294 (Box 17, Folder 645)
  - Box 8, folder 296 (Box 17, Folder 646)
  - Box 8, folder 300 (Box 17, Folder 647)
  - Box 9, folders 304-314 (Box 17, Folder 648-649)
  - Box 10, folder 321 (Box 17, Folder 650)
  - Box 10, folder 322 (Box 17, Folder 651)
  - Box 10, folder 324 (Box 17, Folder 652)
  - Box 10, folder 325 (Box 17, Folder 653)
  - Box 10, folder 329 (Box 17, Folder 654)
  - Box 10, folder 331 (Box 17, Folder 655)
  - Box 10, folder 334 (Box 17, Folder 656)
  - Box 10, folder 335 (Box 17, Folder 657)
  - Box 10, folder 336 (Box 17, Folder 658)
  - Box 10, folder 339 (Box 17, Folder 659)
  - Box 10, folders 341-42 (Box 17, Folder 660)
  - Box 10, folder 343 (Box 17, Folder 661)
  - Box 10, folders 346-347 (Box 17, Folder 662)
  - Box 10, folder 351 (Box 18, Folder 663)
  - Box 11, folder 352 (Box 18, Folder 664)
  - Box 11, folder 355 (Box 18, Folder 665)
  - Box 11, folder 363 (Box 18, Folder 666)
  - Box 11, folder 365 (Box 18, Folder 667)
  - Box 11, folder 366 (Box 18, Folder 668)
  - Box 11, folder 367 (Box 18, Folder 669)
  - Box 11, folder 369 (Box 18, Folder 670)
  - Box 11, folder 370 (Box 18, Folder 671)
  - Box 11, folder 371 (Box 18, Folder 672)
  - Box 11, folder 373 (Box 18, Folder 673)
  - Box 11, folder 374 (Box 18, Folder 674)
  - Box 11, folder 375 (Box 18, Folder 675)
  - Box 11, folder 376 (Box 18, Folder 676)
  - Box 11, folder 377 (Box 18, Folder 677)
  - Box 11, folder 382 (Box 18, Folder 678)
  - Box 11, folder 383 (Box 18, Folder 679)
  - Box 11, folder 387 (Box 18, Folder 680)
  - Box 11, folder 388 (Box 18, Folder 681)
  - Box 11, folder 394 (Box 18, Folder 682)
  - Box 11, folder 395 (Box 18, Folder 683)
  - Box 12, folders 397-398 (Box 18, Folder 684)
  - Box 12, folder 403 (Box 18, Folder 685)
  - Box 12, folder 404 (Box 18, Folder 686)
  - Box 12, folder 407 (Box 18, Folder 687)
  - Box 12, folder 410 (Box 18, Folder 688)
  - Box 12, folder 411 (Box 18, Folder 689)
  - Box 12, folder 412 (Box 18, Folder 690)
  - Box 12, folder 414 (Box 18, Folder 691)
  - Box 12, folder 415 (Box 18, Folder 692)
  - Box 12, folder 417 (Box 18, Folder 693)
  - Box 12, folder 418 (Box 18, Folder 694)
  - Box 12, folder 419 (Box 18, Folder 695)